subhub.com 2005-12-24

# SubHub - Powerful Subscription Web sites - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### SITEOWNER PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY

Welcome to our Privacy Policy. 

This explains what we do with the personal information that the Siteowner (“you”, “your”) give us and the personal information we receive from the end-users of your website (the “Site”).  If you have not already done so, please read our Service Agreement before reading this Privacy Policy. In summary, we use the personal information that we collect from you and the end-users of the Site to allow you to use the Services offered by us.  This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and not to any other company, individual, organisation or website that you may reach via a link from the Site, except for those companies we mention below.  If at any time you have a question about anything contained in this Privacy Policy or a general query on privacy, please contact us at:

SubHub Limited  
Riverside   
Meads Lane  
Wheathampstead  
Herts  
AL4 8BZ

Email: [privacy@subhub.com](mailto:privacy@subhub.com)

 **Consent**

Your use of our Service signifies your consent to us collecting and using personal information about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should we choose to change our Privacy Policy for any reason, we will send you details by email to the address you have provided to us.

The end-users use of the Site signifies their consent to us collecting and using their personal information about them in accordance with the end-user privacy policy. 

**How we collect information from you and the end-users**

In order to provide you with the Service, you will need to provide us with some personal details and business information including those that you provide in the sign up form.

In order to develop and maintain the Site as part of the Service we will have access to your personal information including information about the Site performance, purchases and transactions and will use that information only in so far as is necessary to maintain and operate the Site.

In order to process payments to you through the Site, WorldPay or such other payment partner as we may use from time to time may provide us with information detailing the credits and/or debits and transactions made to you through the Site.

In order to design and host the Site, Netsight Internet Solutions Ltd of Bristol, UK or such designer or host provider as we may use from time to time may provide us with information detailing Site performance and transactions made to you through the Site.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small files of information which are stored on your computer.  Web sites you visit ask your computer to store this information and retrieve the information from your computer so that they can keep track of things like other web sites you visit or how you navigate our website or other files which provide you with the Site.  For more information about what cookies are and how they work, visit www.allaboutcookies.org. 

On revisiting our website or in using the files, our computer server will recognise the cookie and give us information about your use of the Site. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance.  If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use the Site but you may find that the Site may not function properly or is slower than when you allow a cookie to be installed on your machine.

 **How we look after your information**

We make sure that all the information we hold on you and the end-users of the Site is as safe as possible. In addition, we have strict security procedures covering the storage and disclosure of your information in order to prevent unauthorised access and to comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. This means that sometimes we may ask you for proof of identity before disclosing any personal information to you.

 **What do we do with your information?**

We use your information to design and maintain the Site including processing orders end-users make from the Site.  We may use the information provided by the end-users to generate information about site performance and effect transactions made through the Site. We may contact you from time to time to let you know about our services which may include sending you newsletters and news on events that you may be interested in.  You can elect not to receive such marketing material at any time by writing to [privacy@subhub.com](mailto:privacy@subhub.com) **.**

 **When do we give information that you provide us with to other people?**

Apart from entities that are involved in helping us to run the Site, we never give your information to any third parties.  The entities that help us run our site are WorldPay and Netsight Internet Solutions Ltd of Bristol, UK, which provides hosting and design services to us.

In order to buy material from the Site you and the end-users will have to comply with the terms of our payment partner, WorldPay, and will need to review and agree to WorldPay’s Privacy Policy (see the WorldPay terms and conditions for further information).  We and WorldPay will share information with each other only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments end-users make through the Site and to enable you to retrieve payments from WorldPay. 

In order to design and host the Site you and the end-users will have to comply with the terms of our design and host provider, Netsight Internet Solutions Ltd of Bristol, UK, and will need to review and agree to Netsight’s Privacy Policy  (see the Netsight terms and conditions for further information). We and Netsight will share information with each other only to the extent necessary for the purpose of providing the Service and maintaining the Site.

We reserve the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information (i) to comply with applicable laws and government requests, (ii) to be able to operate our systems properly or (iii) to protect ourselves or our users.

 **How to contact us**

If you ever want to change any information you have provided to us please contact us at [privacy@subhub.com](mailto:privacy@subhub.com).  You can always get in contact with us at the address above, send a fax or phone us. ****
